Eric Tsai UI/UX Designer



About Me

I've been designing and coding web and mobile interfaces for 5 years. Much of my experience has been with silicon valley startups and agencies on many websites and app projects. I'm always learning and taking on new challenges in design and entrepreneurship.



VISUAL DESIGN

Illustrator, Sketch, Photoshop, and Paper and Pen



FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

HTML/CSS, Sublime Text, LESS/SASS, JQuery, and Git



UX PROTOTYPING

Origami, Form, Wireframes, and A/B tests

Work Experience

JUN 2016

Product Designer

JUL 2015

Product Designer

FEB 2015

Product Designer

FEB 2014

Product Designer

CLOUDFLARE (Jun 2016 - Current)

I'm the first designer on the new design team working primarily on the web app UI/UX. Creating key wireframe prototypes and user interview research. It's also my role to set up our design process, hiring and build the design team and set the direction of design culture at Cloudflare, www.cloudflare.com

RUNSCOPE (Jul 2015 - Mar 2016)

I was part of the Ghost Inspector Team to rebuild the marketing website and redesigned the app experience. I sketched, mocked-up, and coded everything on the front-end and helped plan out the direction of Ghost Inspector and the groundwork for new features. www.ghostinspector.com

TELEBORDER (Feb 2015 - Jun 2015)

Y-Combinator S13 company. I worked as the first designer, focused on redesigning the user experience, branding, and all front end styles. I worked with the development, product, and marketing teams to build the web app. www.teleborder.com

TRUTH - JUST SAY IT! (Feb 2014 - Oct 2014)

I was the first employee and was part of an accelerator program in Montreal. I was in charge of all design, marketing and some growth planning; we hit 20,000 users with over a quarter million messages sent by the end of the first year. www.usetruth.com

Eric Tsai UI/UX Designer



NOV 2013

UI Designer

MINACORE ENGINEERING, LTD. (Oct 2013 - Feb 2014)

I was tasked by Shell Canada to create an automated system to monitor plant safety conditions and maintenance. I designed the UI to be fast to read and accurate to interpret. The final UI was also used by other major mining corporations.

JUNE 2011

Web & Print Designer

AMPLUS DESIGN AND MARKETING, INC. (May 2011 - Oct 2013)

I co-founded one of the top agencies in Vancouver. We designed many websites, branding, and marketing for many top clients including AirChina and Holiday Inn. www.amplusmarketing.com

Personal Work

FEB 2016

UI/UX Designer

AUG 2012

App Designer

LAUNCH HACK - PERRY (Feb 2015)

We created a natural language processing travel assistant using Wit.ai. Other components included: logo, design and styled the front-end and trained the Al. Our project made it through to the second round of judging.

SPACEFLUX LABS (Aug 2013)

I collaborated with a friend to create an android app in a month. We designed the app in Illustrator then built the app on Cordova for Android.

http://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.phonegap.zen_wallpapers_hd

Education & Accelerator

FOUNDERFUEL ACCELERATOR ALUMNUS (Feb 2014 – April 2014)

Winter 2014 Cohort. Montreal, Canada.

http://www.founderfuel.com/en/

SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY ALUMNUS (Sept 2007 – June 2011)

B.A, Interactive Arts and Technology: Design Concentration. Vancouver, Canada.

http://www.siat.sfu.com/